// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Consider this statement: 'I now pronounce you as husband and wife.' Who among the following can say this and make marital union happen?",
    answer: "a. priest",
    options: [
      "a. priest",
      "b. teacher",
      "c. retired policeman",
      "d. famous celebrity"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What do you think does the speaker mean when he/she says, 'Can you carry these for me?'",
    answer: "b. The speaker is requesting me to help him/her carry his things.",
    options: [
      "a. The speaker wants to know if I have the ability to carry his/her things.",
      "b. The speaker is requesting me to help him/her carry his things.",
      "c. The speaker does not make sense.",
      "d. The speaker does not mean anything."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "You and your sibling were playing in your room. Suddenly, your mother entered the room and she angrily said, 'It’s dirty here!' How would you interpret what she said?",
    answer: "b. She wants you to clean the room.",
    options: [
      "a. She feels happy.",
      "b. She wants you to clean the room.",
      "c. She does not feel well that is why she got angry.",
      "d. She just wants to get angry."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Based on the scenario in item number 3, what will your next action be?",
    answer: "c. I will stop playing with my sibling and will clean the room.",
    options: [
      "a. I will continue playing with my sibling.",
      "b. I will agree with her and say that the room is dirty.",
      "c. I will stop playing with my sibling and will clean the room.",
      "d. I will ignore my mother."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In which of the following statements is the speaker making a commitment?",
    answer: "c. 'I promise to help you with your problems.'",
    options: [
      "a. 'I checked her outputs last week.'",
      "b. 'I am sad and feeling blue!'",
      "c. 'I promise to help you with your problems.'",
      "d. 'I think following the law makes us responsible citizens.'"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following refers to the utterance that a speaker makes in order to achieve an intended effect?",
    answer: "a. Speech Act",
    options: [
      "a. Speech Act",
      "b. Speech Demo",
      "c. Speech Style",
      "d. Speech Variation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The following are the known functions of speech act EXCEPT:",
    answer: "d. planning",
    options: [
      "a. apology",
      "b. greeting",
      "c. offering",
      "d. planning"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "'Please clean the house.' This utterance falls under _____ type of speech act.",
    answer: "c. illocutionary",
    options: [
      "a. commissive",
      "b. locutionary",
      "c. illocutionary",
      "d. permissive"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "This refers to the audience’s reaction to an utterance since it carries a directive for the audience.",
    answer: "c. perlocutionary",
    options: [
      "a. locutionary",
      "b. illocutionary",
      "c. perlocutionary",
      "d. speech act"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The listed ideas are utterance requirements for Locutionary Act, EXCEPT FOR ONE.",
    answer: "c. has the appropriate response to what has been said",
    options: [
      "a. has sense which is more important for communication to take place",
      "b. has the same meaning to both the speaker and the listener",
      "c. has the appropriate response to what has been said",
      "d. has value to shared meaning when it is modified or adjusted"
    ]
  },
];
